Guide to the Donald Jay Grout papers,1929-2002.
Grout, Donald Jay papers
- Series IV. The Operas of Alessandro Scarlatti
  - Unpublished manuscript scores, libretti and notes.
    - Gli equivoci nel sembiante, libretto (Rome, 1679) (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Gli equivoci nel sembiante, libretto (Rome, 1680) (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Gli equivoci nel sembiante, libretto (Siena, 1680) (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Gli equivoci nel sembiante, libretto (Naples, 1681) (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Bologna (Civ. mus.) 6314 - Gli equivoci nel sembiante, libretto (Ravenna, 1685) (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Gli amori fortunati [=Gli equivoci nel sembiante], libretto (Venice, 1690) (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Gli amori fortunati [=Gli equivoci nel sembiante], libretto (Venice, 1690) (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Gli equivoci nel sembiante, libretto (Padua, 1716) (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms. 32.2.31 - A. Scarlatti, Arie dell'Odicea e Berenice, 1701 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - British Museum, Ms. Add. 14, 163 - A. Scarlatti, Laodicea e Berenice Cantata a voce sola (fragments), 1701 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Paris (Bibl. du Cons.), Ms D 11,906 - A. Scarlatti, arie della Laodicea, 1695 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Paris (Bibl. Nat.), Ms VM 416 - A. Scarlatti, Laodicea e Berenice(Act I), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Paris (Bibl. Nat.), Ms VM 416 - A. Scarlatti, Laodicea e Berenice(Act II), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Paris (Bibl. Nat.), Ms VM 416 - A. Scarlatti, Laodicea e Berenice(Act III), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Lib. 6671 - Laodicea e Berenice, libretto (Naples, 1701) (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Berlin Staatsbibliothek, 19,641 - A. Scarlatti, Mitridate Eupatore (Act I), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Berlin Staatsbibliothek, 19,641 - A. Scarlatti, Mitridate Eupatore (Act II), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Berlin Staatsbibliothek, 19,641 - A. Scarlatti, Mitridate Eupatore (Act III), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Berlin Staatsbibliothek, 19,641 - A. Scarlatti, Mitridate Eupatore (Act IV), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Berlin Staatsbibliothek, 19,641 - A. Scarlatti, Mitridate Eupatore (Act V), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms 33.3.12 - A. Scarlatti, Ariette from Mutio Scevola, 1698 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms 33.5.39 - A. Scarlatti, ariettine diverse de l'opera intitolata Il Nerone, 1695 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms 33.3.17 - A. Scarlatti, arie delle Nozze col nemico (I), 1695 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms 33.3.17 - A. Scarlatti, arie delle Nozze col nemico (II), 1695 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms 32.2.32 - A. Scarlatti, arie dell' Odoardo, 1700 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Paris (Bibl. du Cons.), Ms.D.11,906 - A. Scarlatti, arie della pastorale Il pastor di Corinto, 1701 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Brussels (Bibl. Royale), Ms.II 3963/1 - A. Scarlatti, Pirro e Demetrio (Act I), n.d. (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Brussels (Bibl. Royale), Ms.II 3963/2 - A. Scarlatti, Pirro e Demetrio (Act II), n.d. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Brussels (Bibl. Royale), Ms.II 3963/3 - A. Scarlatti, Pirro e Demetrio (Act III), n.d. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms.II 32.2.34 - A. Scarlatti, Pirro e Demetrio (Act I), 1694 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms.II 32.2.34 - A. Scarlatti, Pirro e Demetrio (Act II), 1694 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms.II 32.2.34 - A. Scarlatti, Pirro e Demetrio (Act III), 1694 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - A. Scarlatti, facsimile autograph manuscript of "De tenebroso lacu" (original in British Museum) from Pirro e Demetrio, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), 33.6.37 - 52 arie from Pirro e Demetrio, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), 34.6.32 - A. Scarlatti, 10 arie from Pirro e Demetrio, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Berkeley, M.33.S37.P5 Case* - A. Scarlatti, Aires+Duets from Pyrrhus e Clotilda [in: The Ladys Entertainment or Banquet of Musick], n.d. (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - A. Scarlatti, Pyrrhus and Demetrius (instrumental parts) (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - British Museum (Music Room), I.355 - A. Scarlatti, "Songs in the New Opera of Pyrrhus and Demetrius" (London, J. Cullen) Pyrrhus e Clotilda [in: The Ladys Entertainment or Banquet of Musick] (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Rome (Bibl. Casanatense) - Pirro e Demetrio, libretto (Venice, 1690) (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Lib. 6948 - Pirro e Demetrio, libretto (Naples, 1694) (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Lib. 6949 - Il Pirro e Demetrio, libretto (Rome, 1694) (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Rome (Bibl. Casanatense) - Pirro e Demetrio, libretto (Milan, 1695) (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Lib. 6950 - Pirro e Demetrio, libretto (Florence, 1696) (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Pirro e Demetrio, libretto (Livorno, 1700) (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - UCLA (Clark Lib.) - Pyrrhus and Demetrius, libretto (London, 1709) (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Brussels (Cons. Royal de musique), MSII 3962 - A. Scarlatti, Il Pompeo, 1683 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Univ. of Washington, Seattle, Ms. Uncat. 650 - A. Scarlatti, arias from Pompeo, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Schatz Collection, Item 1732 Pompeo, libretto, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.) 5116 - La Principessa fedele, libretto (Naples 1710) (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Bologna (Bibl. Univ.) - La Principessa Fedele, libretto (Genoa, 1713) (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Paris (Bibl. du Cons.), Ms. D. 11,901 - A. Scarlatti, La Rosaura, Act I, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Paris (Bibl. du Cons.), Ms. D. 11,901 - A. Scarlatti, La Rosaura, Act II, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - British Museum, Ms. Add. 14, 167 - A. Scarlatti, La Rosaura, Act I, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - British Museum, Ms. Add. 14, 167 - A. Scarlatti, La Rosaura, Act II, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - British Museum, Ms. Add. 14, 167 - A. Scarlatti, La Rosaura, Act III, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - British Museum, Ms. Add. 31,513 - A. Scarlatti, La Rosaura, Act I, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - British Museum, Ms. Add. 31,513 - A. Scarlatti, La Rosaura, Act II, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - British Museum, Ms. Add. 31,513 - A. Scarlatti, La Rosaura, Act III, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Florence (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms. B. 2379 - A. Scarlatti, La Rosaura[Gli equivoci in amore], n.d. (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Rome (Bibl. Vat.), Barb. Lat. 4155 (from I: RVat) - A. Scarlatti, 11 arie from Gli equivoci in amore[Parts] I, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Vienna (Nat. Bibl.), Suppl. Mus. 1086 - A. Scarlatti, La Rosaura[Parts] I, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Vienna (Nat. Bibl.), Suppl. Mus. 1086 - A. Scarlatti, La Rosaura[Parts] II, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Gli equivoci in amore (=La Rosaura), libretto (Rome, 1690) (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Lib 7053 - La Rosaura, libretto (Naples, 1690), 1691 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Gli equivoci in amore, libretto (Rome, 1691) (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Florence (Biblioteca Marucelliana) - La Rosaura di Cipro, libretto (Florence, 1692) (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Gli equivoci in amore (=La Rosalba), libretto (Naples, 1692) (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Gli equivoci in amore (=La Rosaura), libretto (Rome, 1692) (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Gli equivoci in amore (=La Rosalba), libretto (Livorno, 1699) (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Bologna (Bibl. Univ.) - La Rosalba, libretto (Livorno, 1699) (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - A. Scarlatti, Rosmene, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3933 - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La Rosmene, Act I, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3933 - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La Rosmene, Act II, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3933 - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La Rosmene, Act III, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Oxford (Bodleian Lib.), Ms. 957 (ff. 109R-130V) - A. Scarlatti, Rosmene (fragments), n.d. (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Rome (Bibl. Vat.), Barb. Lat. 4173 - A. Scarlatti: Aria "Che cos'è quest' honestà" (from Rosmene), n.d. (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms. 33.4.10 - A. Scarlatti, 2 Arie: "Son ferito," "Per meglio stringere"(from Rosmene), n.d. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - La Rosmene notes from D. Moroney (also Mitridate), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Scipione nelle Spagne, libretto (Naples, 1714) (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 177, H1-14 - A. Scarlatti, Statira (fragments/arias) [1p. recit by Gasparini ?], n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Brussels (Cons. Royal de musique), 21, 853 - La Statira, libretto (Rome 1690) (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), 32.2.36 - A. Scarlatti, Tiberio imperatore d'oriente(Arie), 1702 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3914, ff 84-107 - A. Scarlatti, Il Tigrane(fragments: comic scenes), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Birmingham University - A. Scarlatti, Il Tigrane(Act I), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Birmingham University - A. Scarlatti, Il Tigrane(Act II), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Birmingham University - A. Scarlatti, Il Tigrane(Act III), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - British Museum, R.M. 23, 628 - A. Scarlatti, Il Tigrane(Act I), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - British Museum, R.M. 23, 628 - A. Scarlatti, Il Tigrane(Act II), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - British Museum, R.M. 23, 628 - A. Scarlatti, Il Tigrane(Act III), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Tigrane material, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Tigrane atto primo (Sinfonia-scene vii photocopies), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Tigrane atto primo (scene vii-end photocopies), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Tigrane atto secondo (scene i-xii photocopies), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Tigrane atto secondo (scene xiii-end photocopies), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Tigrane atto terzo (scene i-xi photocopies), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Tigrane atto terzo(scene xii-finale photocopies), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Tigrane photocopy of partial mss. score, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Paris (Bibl. du Cons.), Ms. D. 11,904 - A. Scarlatti, Tito Sempronio Gracco, Arie (I), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Paris (Bibl. du Cons.), Ms. D. 11,904 - A. Scarlatti, Tito Sempronio Gracco, Arie (II), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms. 32.2.37 - A. Scarlatti, Tito Sempronio Gracco(Act I), 1702 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms. 32.2.37 - A. Scarlatti, Tito Sempronio Gracco(Act II), 1702 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms. 32.2.37 - A. Scarlatti, Tito Sempronio Gracco(Act III), 1702 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Tito Sempronico Graccho, libretto (Naples, 1702) (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Tito Sempronico Graccho, libretto (Palermo, 1702) (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Lib. 5128 - Tito Sempronico Graccho, libretto (Rome, 1720) (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Vienna (Bibl. Nat.) - A. Scarlatti, Telemaco(Autograph), n.d. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3895 - A. Scarlatti, Il Telemacho (Act I), n.d. (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3895 - A. Scarlatti, Il Telemacho (Act II), n.d. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3895 - A. Scarlatti, Il Telemacho (Act III), n.d. (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Paris (Bibl. du Cons.), Ms. D. 11, 902-1 - A. Scarlatti, Il Telemacho (Act I), n.d. (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Paris (Bibl. du Cons.), Ms. D. 11, 902-2 - A. Scarlatti, Il Telemacho (Act II), n.d. (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Paris (Bibl. du Cons.), Ms. D. 11, 902-2 - A. Scarlatti, Il Telemacho (Act III), n.d. (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - I: Rc Ms. 2221 - A. Scarlatti, Cantate (incl. 2 items from Telemacho), n.d. (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Ms. D.D.57 - A. Scarlatti, Quartetto "Sdegno troppo fiero" from Il Telemacho, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Lib. 5124 - Telemaco, libretto (Rome, 1718) (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Library of Congress - Il trionfo dell'onore (Act I), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Library of Congress - Il trionfo dell'onore (Act II), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Library of Congress - Il trionfo dell'onore (Act III), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - British Museum - Il trionfo dell'onore (Act I), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - British Museum - Il trionfo dell'onore (Act II), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - British Museum - Il trionfo dell'onore (Act III), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - A. Scarlatti, Il Trionfo dell'onore, (vocal score by Virgilio Mortari), 1964 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - British Museum - A. Scarlatti, Il trionfo d'amore(1718) (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Il Trionfo dell'onore translated by Vanni Bartolozzi, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Il Trionfo dell'onore microprint beginning of Act III, Napoli 1718 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Tutto il male (portion of Act I), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Other material related to all volumes of The Operas of Alessandro Scarlatti
    - Scarlatti Opera Editions, style sheet 1970 and 1974 revisions, 1970/1974 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Scarlatti materials received from Joseph Kerman, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Introduction to The Operas of Alessandro Scarlatti
    - Chapters I-III, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Chapters IV-V, Epilogue, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Discarded music examples, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - "Not going to be used", 1978 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Index, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Title pages, footnotes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Chapter II, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Chapter III, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Chapter IV, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Chapter V, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Chapter VI, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Berkeley Lectures 1977-1978
    The Operas of Alessandro Scarlatti
    - Berkeley Lectures - Memoranda, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Berkeley I, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Berkeley Lectures - Chapter I, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Berkeley II, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Berkeley notes, mostly for II, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Berkeley IIIA and III, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Notes for Lecture III, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Berkeley IV, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Berkeley V, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Berkeley VI, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Berkeley VI notes, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Berkeley memorabilia, 1975 - 1976 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - The Operas of Alessandro Scarlatti
    Editorial Correspondence
    - Scarlatti: Austria – Wien - Riethus, P., 1967-1969 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Scarlatti: Germany – Kassel – Deutsch Musikgeschichtliches Archiv (Kassel: Dtsch. Musikg. Archiv, RISM), 1966-1970 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Scarlatti: Germany – Kassel – Landgraf-Moritz-Stiftung (Kassel: Ldgrf. Moritz-Stiftung), 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Scarlatti: Landgraf-Moritz-Stiftung, 1975-1978 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Scarlatti: Germany – Würzburg - Osthoff, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Modena Bibliotea Estense (I: Moe), 1966-1969 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Montecassino. Biblioteca (I: MONTECASSINO), 1966-1975 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Naples – Conservatino S. Pietro (I: Nc), 1966-1973 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Naples. Padri Gerolamini (Fr. Borrelli) (I:Nf), 1966-1967 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Palermo –Biblioteca Communale, Laboratorio Fotografica (I: PLco), 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Parma Conservatorio de Musica "A. Bioto" (I: Pac), 1967-1969 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Pesaro – Biblioteca del Liceo Musicale (I: PESc), 1973 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Rome – Biblioteca Casanatense (I: Rc), 1970 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Roma: Deutsches Historisches Institut, 1965-1976 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Rome – Santa Cecilia (I: Rsc), 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Rome-Vatican (I: Rvat), 1967-1969 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Scarlatti: Italy – Rome - Vivarelli, 1969-1972 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Rovigo - Accademia dei Concordi (I: Rovigo Acc. dei Concordi), 1970 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Scarlatti: Italy – Siena – Biblioteca Communale (I: Sc), 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Scarlatti: Italy – Venezia – Biblioteca Nazionale Marciana (I: Vnm), 1969 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Scarlatti: Switzerland – Basel - Oesch, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Scarlatti: U. S. – University of California, Berkeley (US: U. of Cal Berkeley), 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Scarlatti: U. S. – UCB - Skaggs Foundation, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Scarlatti: Los Angeles – UCLA Clark Memorial Library (US:LA), 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Scarlatti: D. C. – Washington - Library of Congress (US:Wc), 1966-1975 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University - Hull Memorial Publication Fund, 1974-1983 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University - Scarlatti – Subsidies D. J. G.'s gifts to Harvard, 1974-1977 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University - Harvard University Press - Contracts / royalty agreements, 1974-1979 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 40)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 41)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts – Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 42)
    - Scarlatti: Massachusetts –Harvard University Press - Scarlatti correspondence, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 43)
    - Scarlatti: US:Vassar=US:PO (Poughkeepsie) (RISM), 1970-1974 (Box 56, Folder 44)
    - Scarlatti: U. S. –Rochester (NY) – Sibley Library (US:R), 1967 (Box 56, Folder 45)
    - Scarlatti: U. S. – Seattle (WA) (US:S), 1970 (Box 56, Folder 46)
    - Scarlatti: (Notes) Phi Mg (Φ Mg), 1973 (Box 56, Folder 47)
    - Scarlatti: Permissions Letter folder, 1972-1982 (Box 56, Folder 48)
    - Scarlatti: Permissions for La cadula, 1977-1982 (Box 56, Folder 49)
    - Scarlatti: Scarlatti Reviews (legal size folder), 1976-1986 (Box 56, Folder 50)
    - Scarlatti: Austria - Wien – Oesterreichische Nationalbibliothek (A:Wn), 1972 (Box 56, Folder 51)
    - Scarlatti: Belgium - Brussels (B:Br), 1968-1976 (Box 56, Folder 52)
    - Scarlatti: B (Belgium):Bc (Brussels Conservatory), 1959-1977 (Box 56, Folder 53)
    - Scarlatti: C(Canada):Mc (Montreal), 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 54)
    - Scarlatti: France - Lyon (F:LY), 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 55)
    - Scarlatti: France – Paris - Bibliothèque Nationale (F:Pn,Pc), 1968-1976 (Box 56, Folder 56)
    - Scarlatti: France - Paris – Comtesse de Chambure (F:Pthibat), 1969 (Box 56, Folder 57)
    - Scarlatti: Germany – Berlin - Staatsbibliothek den Stiftung Preussischer Kulturbesitz (D:Bds), 1965-1976 (Box 56, Folder 58)
    - Scarlatti: Germany - Dresden – Sächsische Landesbibliothek (D:Dl), 1966-1975 (Box 56, Folder 59)
    - Scarlatti: Germany – Munich Bayerische Staatsbibliothek, Musiksammlung (D:Mbs), 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 60)
    - Scarlatti: Germany - Münster, Bischöfliche Kirchenmusikschule (D:MÜks), 1966-1976 (Box 56, Folder 61)
    - Scarlatti: Great Britain - Birmingham University (GB:Bu), 1966 (Box 56, Folder 62)
    - Scarlatti: Great Britain - Cambridge – Fitzwilliam Museum (GB:Cfm), 1967-1975 (Box 56, Folder 63)
    - Scarlatti: Great Britain – Cambridge - King's College (GB:Ckc), 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 64)
    - Scarlatti: Great Britain - Cambridge, Magdalene College (GB:Cmc), 1970-1975 (Box 56, Folder 65)
    - Scarlatti: Great Britain - Cardiff – Public Library (GB:CDp) (see also Boyd), 1967-1969 (Box 56, Folder 66)
    - Scarlatti: Great Britain – London, British Museum (GB:Lfm), 1966-1976 (Box 56, Folder 67)
    - Scarlatti: Great Britain – London - BBC (British Broadcasting Corporation), 1968-1979 (Box 56, Folder 68)
    - Scarlatti: Great Britain – Oxford Christ Church Library (GB:Och), 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 69)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Bologna (I:Bu), 1967-1974 (Box 56, Folder 70)
    - Scarlatti: Italy – Bologna - Civico Museo Bibliografico Musicale (I:Bc), 1974-1977 (Box 56, Folder 71)
    - Scarlatti: Italy – Bologna - Civico Museo Bibliografico Musicale (I:Bc), 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 72)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Firenze – Marucelliana (I:Fm etc.), 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 73)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Macerata: Biblioteca Comunale (I:MAC), 1970 (Box 56, Folder 74)
    - Scarlatti: Italy - Milano – Biblioteca del Conservatorio di Musica G. Verdi (I:Mc), 1969 (Box 56, Folder 75)
    - Scarlatti: Italy – Milano - Sartori (I:Mb) (see also Braidense), 1966-1976 (Box 56, Folder 76)
    - Scarlatti: Italy – Venezia - Fondazione Giorgio Cini (I:Cini), 1969-1974 (Box 56, Folder 77)
    - Scarlatti: Fritz Rikko, Juilliard School of Music, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 78)
    - Scarlatti: Giancarlo Rostirolla, Nuova Rivista Musicale Italiana, Roma, 1973-1977 (Box 56, Folder 79)
    - Scarlatti: H. Colin Slim, University of California, Irvine, 1970-1980 (Box 56, Folder 80)
    - Scarlatti: Edward Swenson, Ithaca College, 1968-1979 (Box 56, Folder 81)
    - Scarlatti: Charles E. Troy, University of Washington, Seattle, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 82)
    - Scarlatti: Thomas Walker, Grove's Dictionary, London, 1969-1975 (Box 56, Folder 83)
    - Scarlatti: Hermine (Mrs. Jay) Williams, 1974-1979 (Box 56, Folder 84)
    - Scarlatti: Christoph Wolff, Harvard University, 1971-1976 (Box 56, Folder 85)
    - Scarlatti: Il Trionfo dell 'Onore, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 86)
    - Scarlatti: Notes made on first inspection of films received, 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 87)
    - Scarlatti: list of editors, 1973-1979 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Scarlatti: Lowell Lindgren, 1975-1979 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Scarlatti: W. C. Holmes, 1968-1985 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Scarlatti: letters sent re Scarlatti ed., 1979-1984 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Scarlatti: "Gli equivoci," D'Accone, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Scarlatti: Harvard, "Ciro," [Gaynor] Jones, 1983-1985 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Scarlatti: Gaynor Jones, 1971-1980 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Scarlatti: [Michael] Collins, 1967-1975 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Scarlatti: Mike Collins - "Tigrane", 1980-1985 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Scarlatti: [Joscelyn] Godwin, 1970-1979 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Scarlatti: Harvard Univ. Scarlatti correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Scarlatti: D. J. G. reprints: The Original Version of Alessandro Scarlatti's 'Griselda' and Opera Seria at the Crossroads: Scarlatti's "Eraclea", n.d. (Box 57, Folder 12)